威尔 · 森特斯: 好了，伙计们。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Okay, folks.
所以我们在这里重新构造这个函数，这个函数接受一个数组。
So we are back building out this function
here that's gonna take in an array.
复制右边，鲍勃先生，它看起来是一个数组，1,2,3在这里，和
Copy right Mr. Bob it was take in an array
by the looks of it, 1, 2, 3 here, and
创建一个新数组，然后循环遍历输入数组。
create a new array, is then gonna iterate
through loop through the input array.
从除两个以外的每个元素模式，用所有填充输出数组
Take each element mode from other than by
two, fill up the output array with all
这些双倍的值和返回的年金填写的数组。
those doubled values and return out
that annuity filled out for the array.
好吧，这是我们的工作，像这样的任务。
Okay, it's something we do,
some sort of task like this.
我们要把它做出来，画出来，然后我们会看到另一个函数
We're gonna build it out, diagram it out,
but we're then gonna see another function
我要试探一下我的最佳位置。
that's going to look,
I'm gonna sound out my best position.
我们会看到另一个函数，这就是为什么我不喜欢讲台。
We're gonna see another function that's,
that's why I don't like podiums.
我们将会看到另一个函数，看起来特别令人沮丧
We're gonna see another function that's
gonna look particularly frustratingly
相似的。
similar.
然而，我们还是要从头开始建造它。
And yet, we're gonna build
it out from scratch, again.
好吧从我们的朋友 Adam 开始。
All right,
let's start with our friend Adam.
开始吧亚当。
Here we go, Adam.
把它拿走。
Take it away.
让我们从这里开始学习我们的代码。
Let's start walking through our code here.
我们在做什么，亚当，在我们代码的第一行？
What are we doing, Adam,
in line one of our code here?
我们在全球记忆中存储了什么，亚当？
What are we storing into Global Memory,
Adam?
扬声器2: 是的，功能定义与标签复印机 a 和乘-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, function definition
with the label copier A and multiply-
威尔 · 森特斯: 非常好，是的,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice, yeah,
函数定义的标签复制数组，要尝试和
the function definition with
the label copy array, gonna try and
保持这个整齐，复制数组，乘以2，很好。
keep this neat, copy array and
multiply by two, excellent.
保存了整个函数定义，就是这样。
The whole function definition is saved,
there we go.
就是这样，复制数组，乘以2，就保存了。
So, there it is, copy array and
multiply by two, it's saved.
现在我们来看看 Matt，我们下一行 JavaScript 代码是什么,
Let's hit up Matt now, with what is our
next line that gets done by JavaScript,
是由 JavaScript 执行的，Matt？
executed by JavaScript, Matt?
我们要定义数组的常数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're gonna define
the constant of my array.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太美了。 谢谢你，马特。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful.
Thank you, Matt.
它有什么价值？
It's got what value?
演讲者2: 一个123的数组。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: An array of 123.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太美了。 谢谢你，马特。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful.
Thank you, Matt.
现在我们到了下一个，马特，继续。
Now we hit the next Matt, keep going.
现在我们来定义结果常数。
Now we're gonna define
the constant of result.
太好了，我真的很喜欢 Matt 大声自信的声音。
Excellent, I'm really enjoying Matt's
loud and confident voice here.
所以我们要继续和马特在一起。
So we're gonna keep staying with Matt.
马特，现在还没有初始化，我们得去做什么？
Matt, it's uninitialized for now,
well we've got to go and do what?
演讲者2: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution context.
执行上下文执行什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution
context to execute what?
复制数组，乘以2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Copy array and
multiply by two.
复制数组并乘以2,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Copy array and
multiply by two,
就是这样，乘以2。
there it is, multiply by two.
我们要把什么作为我们的论点？
And we're gonna pass in
what as our argument?
演讲者2: 我的阵列 威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，也就是一，二,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: My array.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, which is one, two,
三，数组一，二，三。
three, the array one, two, three.
让我们创建一个全新的-扬声器3: 执行上下文。
Let's create that brand new-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 干得好，伙计们。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well done, people.
而我只是得到我的优势在这里。
While I just get my edge here.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 好的，这是执行上下文，这是。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Okay, there is
the execution context, here it is.
让我们把调用堆栈，我们很好。
Let's just put on the call stack,
we're good.
我们在录这个版本，对吧？
We're recording this version,
right, aren't we?
所以我们要把我们所有的东西都放得格外完整。
So we're gonna be extra complete
in all our, all our stuff.
为了子孙后代。
So that for posterity.
我们有，是的，复制，数组。
We have, yeah, copy, array.
乘以2，我们正在运行它，它在我们的调用堆栈上。
Multiply by 2, we're running it,
it's on our call stack.
我保证，我们总是有全球化的，第二次进攻。
We always have global,
come to second down, I promise.
我们总是有全球性的，我做错什么了吗？
We always have global,
did I get anything wrong?
演讲者2: 不，你刚刚明白了，我要问的是全球化。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, you just got it,
I was gonna ask about the global.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 好极了，全球化在那里，我刚刚拿到了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent,
global's there on the, I did just get it,
很好，[笑]正确答案，做得好。
excellent, [LAUGH] correct answer,
well done well.
现在，这是我们的执行环境。
And now, here's our execution context.
执行线程在左手边一行一行地通过代码
With the thread of execution going through
the code line by line on the left hand
我不会总是写出每一行代码
side here, I'm not gonna always
write out every line of code, but
我们大概要经历一下死刑的过程。
roughly we're going through
the thread of execution.
运行代码，这是我们的本地内存。
Running the code, and
then here's our local memory.
马特，交还给你。
Matt, back to you.
在我们当地的记忆中，第一件事是什么？
What is the first thing
in our local memory?
我们马上要在里面储存什么？
What are we storing in there immediately?
我们的数组参数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Our array parameter.
是的，用什么论点？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes,
with assigned what argument?
讲者二: 一二三。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: One two three.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，一二三，就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yep,
one two three, there it is.
我的数组拍摄，填充一个数组，一二三。
My array shot in,
fills an array, one two three.
那么，丹，我们接下来要唱哪一行？
Then Dan, we hit what line next?
现在我们来看函数的主体。
We hit the body of the function now.
谁说要做什么？
Which says to do what?
演讲者2: 我们想创建一个新的常量输出。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We want to
create a new constant output.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 他说得对，干得好，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He's spot on,
well done, exactly.
分配一个什么？
And assign a what?
说话人2: 一个空数组。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A empty array.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 丹说得太好了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent from Dan.
现在我们点击 for 循环。
Now we hit our for loop.
就是这个，for loop。
Here it is, for loop.
我们不会深入到你怎么知道它是声明的，但是
We're not gonna go into the intricacies
of how you know it's declared but
我们知道它的身体之间的位的花括号这一行是
we know that the body of it the bit
between the curly braces that line is
要做 x 次。
gonna be done X number of times.
多少次？
How many number of times?
只要 i 小于数组的长度，我看到,
As long as I is less than the length
of the array, I saw zero,
数组的长度是3，我们每次都要增加 i。
the length of the array's three, we're
gonna increment increase I each time.
然后我们将运行这条线，只要我继续减少或
And then we're going to run that line
as long as I continues to be less or
零继续是,
zero continues to be,
我可以做到小于数组的长度，所以应该是三倍。
I can do to be less than the length of
the array, so that's gonna be three times.
我们会看到它在文件夹的正文中发挥作用。
We're gonna see it play out into
the body of the folder we go.
我把这些放在左边,
I'm going to put these on
the left-hand side here,
不是复制它们，只是为了更容易地使用它们。
not copying them, but just so
we can work with them more easily.
我们有数组123和
We have our array one two three and
我们的输出是空数组 Kayla？
our output is an empty array, Kayla?
让我们来看看 for 循环的主体。
Let's hit the body of the for loop.
数组位置0是什么，凯拉？
Array position zero is what, Kayla?
讲者4: 一。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: One.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 一，我们选择一个，然后用它做什么，凯拉？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: One, we take the one and
we do what with it, Kayla?
说话人4: 我们把它乘以2-Will Sentance: x 当我们得到2时，我们就乘以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: We multiply it by 2-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: x when we get 2 we do
怎么回事 Kayla？
what with that, Kayla?
音箱4: 我们把它推入输出阵列。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: We push it
into the output array.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们推入输出数组，它在那里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We push into
the output array, there it is.
第二，漂亮，干得好。
Two, beautiful, good job.
凯拉，太棒了。
Kayla, excellent.
下一个凯拉，这次我的价值是什么？
Next one Kayla,
this time I's value is what?
讲者4:2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: 2.
威尔 · 森特斯: 这就对了，别担心，我的价值是下次。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There you go
don't worry, i's value next time.
讲者4:1 威尔 · 森特斯: 不要担心，人们,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: 1.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Don't worry people,
在我的新火锅里，我实际上只是迭代了一下
in my new hot pot I literally
only iterate to section make
人们每次都会犯这种错误。
people consistently get that
wrong every single time.
因为归根结底，这是一只蝙蝠。
Because in the end, this is a bat.
这是一个过时的数据界面。
It's a dated interface for data.
但是如果我有一个数据集合，我并不真正关心索引的位置
But if I've got a collection of data, I
don't really care about the index position
大多数时候，我只是想得到下一个元素。
most of the time,
I just want to get the next element.
很明显，这里有一个过时的界面，用来访问数据。
And there's obviously a dated
interface dated way of accessing data.
我把我的数据当作一个不合时宜的文件，这样更好。
I take my data like a anachronistic
document any better is it.
好吧，一个老式的，我想说，就像一个不完美的设计，或者,
[LAUGH] Okay, an old fashioned I'd say,
like a not perfectly designed, or,
因为我们大部分时间都不在乎索引,
because we don't really care about
the index most of the time we're using it,
我们只是想得到元素。
we just wanna get the element.
现在有了新的方法，我们仍然坚持传统的方法。
And there are new ways of doing it, we're
sticking with the traditional way here.
这就是我要说的，我们不会经历
That's what I was gonna say,
we're not gonna go through the for
循环的过程，但这是一个有趣的数据接口。
loop's sort of journey, but
it is an interesting interface for data.
Kayla 向我们展示了为什么,
And Kayla sort of showed us there why,
ultimately,
每次像凯拉这样经验丰富的工程师。
seasoned engineers every time
like Kayla will still go.
不管怎样，你明白我的意思。
Anyway, you get the point.
就是这样，位置1，到达2，拿着它,
So there it is, position 1,
get to 2, take it,
乘以2得到4，把它推到输出。
multiplied by 2 to get 4,
push it to output.
现在我们知道了。
There we have it.
所以对于循环，我们再做一次。
So for loops, we do it again.
好了，2,4,6。
There we go, 2, 4, 6.
现在最后一行 Kayla，复制数组乘以2表示做什么？
And now the final line Kayla, of copy
array multiplied by 2 says to do what?
音箱4: 我们返回输出数组。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: We return the output array.
是的，我们将输出的值返回到全局常量,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, we return the
value of output into what global constant,
凯拉？
Kayla?
讲者四: 结果。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Result.
威尔 · 句子: 结果，很好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into result, well on.
就是这样，伙计们。
And there it is, folk.
我们接受了1,2,3，我们运行了 copyArrayMultipleBy2,
We took in one, two, three, we ran
copyArrayMultipleBy2 on that argument,
我们创建了一个全新的数组
we've created a brand new array and
返回的数组中填充了我们的双倍元素。
returned out that array filled
in with our doubled elements.
任务完成得很好，很好。
Good task, there we go, great.
等一下，杰森。
One second, Jason.
干得好，各位。
Well done, everybody.
你喜欢这个功能。
You love this function.
你会喜欢我的下一个功能的。
[LAUGH] You're gonna
love my next function.
我甚至不想开始说我的下一个功能是多么令人兴奋。
I don't even wanna get started on
how exciting my next function is.
看看这个。
Look at this one.
它动了，动的时候就不那么引人注目了。
[LAUGH] It moved,
it's less compelling when it moves.
好了，大家都看到这里的变化了。
Okay, everyone can see how much
it's changing here, people.
一个字符。
One character.
字面上的意思是一个字符，没错。
Literally one character, exactly.
你认为什么发生了变化？
What do you think has changed?
一切都是一样的，但我们要重建它，因为我们
Everything's the same, but we're gonna
rebuild it from scratch because we
想要感受我们的，威尔 · 森塔斯: 肠子，可以这么说。
want to feel in our,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Gut, so to speak.
这是有问题的，必须有一个更好的方式。
That this is problematic, and
there must be a better way.